oola.com 2018-01-27

# Privacy Policy - Oola.com

Effective as of September 21, 2015

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Gateway Blend, LLC, a Missouri corporation (“Oola”) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (“you,” “your,” or “User”) of its www.oola.com website, platforms, applications, and any derivative or affiliated websites on which this Privacy Policy is posted (collectively, the “Site”).  Oola reserves the right, at its discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time by posting such changes to this page.  You understand that you have the affirmative obligation to check this Privacy Policy periodically for changes, and you hereby agree to periodically review this Privacy Policy for such changes.  The continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy constitutes an acceptance of those changes. 

Oola is based, and this website is hosted, in the United States of America.  If you are from the European Union, Canada or other regions of the world with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law and you are registering an account on the Site, visiting the Site, purchasing products or services from Oola or the Site, or otherwise using the Site, please note that any personally identifiable information that you provide to Oola may be transferred to or utilized by Oola or its affiliates in the United States.  Any such personally identifiable information provided may be processed and stored in the United States by Oola or a service provider acting on its behalf. 

If you are opposed to any of the terms listed below, we ask that you please abstain from using Oola.

**1\. Information Collected**

Oola understands the importance of maintaining your privacy, and strives to provide services with your security in mind. You will be asked for consent if your personal information is to be used in a way other than originally intended. For us to identify which areas of Oola are used the most and provide statistical analysis of the site, we will record information such as your browser type, IP address, timestamp information and the pages you've viewed. This will help us make site enhancements and offer you the highest quality experience possible

Oola will ask you for and keep a record of personal information, including name, email address, login time, and Facebook profile photo. You may change these details and settings on your account page. Submissions you make through Oola may be saved or exhibited publicly on the website, in order to provide the most complete version of our services. "Submissions" refers to any material you post to Oola or information displayed on your profile.

Oola may also collect information about how Users use the Site, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the Site, or the domains and Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses from which Users originate.  While not all of the information that Oola collects from Users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide Oola through the Site or otherwise.  Additionally, certain information regarding your computer systems, network locations, IP address and software may be communicated to Oola in certain circumstances by the digital rights management systems associated with certain Content that you download or access via the Site in order to prevent unauthorized use or distribution of the associated Content.  Non-personally identifiable information collected by Oola (such as patterns of utilization) is exclusively owned by Oola and may be used as it sees fit in accordance with applicable law.

We will record certain information that you provide in feedback, questions, or registered complaints in order to efficiently respond to your questions or concerns.

**2\. Information Disclosure**

By reading this, you acknowledge and accept that Oola is not responsible for information that may be intercepted while being transferred through the Internet.  By reading this, you also release Oola from any claims that surface due to information interception. Even though you may find links and access to unaffiliated third-party sites on Oola, we are not accountable for any privacy practices related to those companies or websites. Please make sure you take time to read the privacy practices of these websites as well.

Oola collects personally identifiable information, such as your name and e-mail address, with your knowledge and consent and uses your personal information to administer the Site and deliver the services you have requested. Oola may use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Oola and its affiliates. Oola may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

The Site automatically collects certain technical information, such as the Internet address from which you visit the Site and your browser type. Oola compiles this information in aggregate form to help diagnose problems with servers and to gather broad demographic information. Oola may use Internet addresses for identification purposes only when necessary to enforce compliance with the Oola Site Terms of Use and to protect its service or any person, as otherwise permitted by law.

Oola will not sell, trade, lend or otherwise voluntarily disclose any personal information that you have provided for any purpose not identified under this Privacy Statement. Oola may share your personal information with third parties to assist in the administration of this Site; to Oola financial and legal advisors; to others as required by law; or for purposes identified from time to time and consented by you. Where personal information is shared with service providers for administrative purposes, we require the service provider to respect this Privacy Policy. Notwithstanding any other provision in this Privacy Policy, in the event someone buys or acquires Oola, or substantially all of its assets, information about you and your use of the Web Site will likely be one of the assets acquired.

**3\. How This Information is Used**

Your personal information may be accessed by affiliates of Oola, such as our parent company, subsidiaries, or joint ventures, that are currently with us or have the potential to be with us in the future. These affiliates are obligated to honor this Privacy Policy. If another company obtains Oola, that company will then possess your personal information. However, they too are under strict obligation to honor the claims of this privacy policy. Third parties that work with Oola may receive submissions you make through the website, which may end up being published on their sites or platforms. This information includes your account name, but not your personal information, unless it was listed in the submission.

Information related to user behavior may be disclosed to third parties in connection with a present or future business partnership. This includes information relating to users that have clicked advertising banners and the number of users visiting our site.

When you visit Oola, you will see advertisements from third parties displayed on the site. Information about your visit to the site may be used by these companies, not including your name, email address, or telephone number. This helps them choose advertisements that you would find most interesting. If you would like more information about not having your information used by third parties, please visit: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google. Google utilizes the data collected to track and examine the use of www.oola.com to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.

Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

Personal data collected: Cookie and Usage Data. Place of processing: USA. Find Google's [privacy policy here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

**4\. Cookies and Web Beacons**

Like most websites, the Site uses cookies and web log files to track site usage.  A cookie is a tiny data file that resides on your computer that allows Oola to recognize you as a User when you return to the Site using the same computer and web browser.  Like the information you enter during account registration, cookie and log file data is used to customize your experience on the Site.  One type of cookie, known as a “persistent” cookie, is set once you have logged in to your Site account.  The next time you visit our Site, the persistent cookie will allow us to recognize you as an existing User so you will not need to log in before using the Site.  In order to access or change any of your private information, you must log in with your password even if your computer contains your persistent cookie.  Additionally, if you log out of the Site you will need to re-enter your password the next time you visit in order to log in to your account.  Another type of cookie, called a “session” cookie, is used to identify a particular visit to the Site.  Session cookies expire after a short time or when you close your web browser.  You can choose to disable cookies on your browser or allow your browser to notify you when a cookie is being sent, however this may prevent you from utilizing certain features of the Site. 

**5\. Security of Personal Information**

Oola maintains reasonable and appropriate measures to secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Oola secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled environment.  You are responsible for ensuring that the computer systems that you use to access the Site have appropriate security controls enabled and you expressly assume the risk of any unauthorized disclosure or intentional intrusion, or of any delay, failure, interruption or corruption of data or other information transmitted in connection with the use of the Site.  You are solely responsible for providing, maintaining and ensure compatibility of all hardware, software, electrical and other physical requirements necessary for your access to and use of the Web Site, or any part thereof. 

Information about Users that is maintained on Oola’s systems is protected using industry standard security measures.  In order to secure your personal information, access to your data is password-protected, and sensitive data is protected by SSL encryption when it is exchanged between your web browser and the Site.  However, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, and Oola cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on or transmitted from its systems will be completely secure.  Oola is not responsible for the circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site by any Users or third parties.

Oola is not responsible for the acts and omission of any third parties related to the security of your connection to the Web Site.

**6\. Privacy Policy Enforcement**

To enforce our privacy policy or to comply with a legal investigation, any information, including personal information, may be referenced.  In compliance with legal procedures such as warrants, statutes, or court orders, your personal information may be distributed to third parties, to take action against illegal activities or to enforce our privacy policy. Oola is not obligated to question the legitimacy of any government request.

**7\. Compliance with the California Privacy Protection Act; DO NOT TRACK**

If you are a California resident and have provided personal information to Oola through the Web Site, you are entitled by law to request certain information regarding any disclosure that may have been made by Oola to third parties of personal information for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, send an email to [feedback@oola.com](mailto:feedback@oola.com) specifying that you seek your “California Customer Choice Privacy Notice.” Please allow thirty (30) days for a response. Oola is required to respond to only one request per customer each year, and is not required to respond to requests made by means other than through the above email address.

We will not share your personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes if you request that we do not do so. If you would like more information about not having your information used by third parties, or if you would like to make such an opt-out request, you may send us an email at [feedback@oola.com](mailto:feedback@oola.com). 

You may also request to opt-out of an advertiser’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative or the Digital Advertising Alliance. You may request to opt-out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting [www.google.com/ads/preferences](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences). All applicable terms on these websites will apply to your request to opt-out in addition to this Privacy Policy.

When contacting us, please indicate your name, address, email address, and what personal information you do not want us to share with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Please note that there is no charge for controlling the sharing of your personal information or for processing this request. At this time, Oola is unable to universally respond to “Do Not Track” or other “opt-out” mechanisms that have been activated by a user through their web browser, and except as otherwise provided herein, does not alter its policies if a user activates such mechanism.

**8\. Compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Act**

We have taken the necessary measures to conform to the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. Our site, services and products are directed for use by people over the age of 13.  We do not collect information from anyone under the age of 13, in any circumstance.

**9\. Privacy Policy Changes**

This Privacy Policy is subject to modifications at any time. Any modifications will be posted to this page. You will be notified via email if any changes regarding the distribution of your personal information are made.

**10\. Contacting Us**

If you have questions, comments, or concerns regarding anything previously stated in the privacy policy or to utilize the rights contracted here please use the [contact form](http://www.oola.com/contact.html) to contact us.
